const data = [
    {
      question: "What does CSS stand for?",
      incorrectAnswers: [
        "Chris Smith Style",
        "50 Crazy Shades of Snore",
        "Classic Seafood/Shrimp Sushi"
      ],
      correctAnswer: "Cascading Style Sheets"
    },
  
    {
      question:
        "What's Xiaxin's biggest secret?",
      incorrectAnswers: [
        "She likes CSS",
        "She likes Chris' smiley face and hug",
        "She likes Chris' accessories and weirdness",
      ],
      correctAnswer: "She likes Chris Smith",
    },
    {
      question: "Does Xiaxin really likes Chris Smith?",
      incorrectAnswers: [
          "Afraid she might not, no matter how mind-blowing handsome Chris is - she likes CSS though.", //"She might not - she prefers CSS instead.", 
          "Who knows?",// The whole world knows? Only she knows? Chris also knew?", 
          "Definitely No - not today - not in a million seconds (11.5740741 days)"
        ],
      correctAnswer: "YES she does!",
    },
    {
      question: "How much does Xiaxin like Chris Smith",
      incorrectAnswers: [
          "Nothing Steve Jobs ever created could fully replace Chris in Xiaxin's life (but she never can afford an airpro/airbook iphone ipad etc).", 
          "She likes Chris slightly more than she likes bacon, but definitely not as much as a pig loves not being bacon.", 
          "She likes Chris almost exactly as much as won't freak him out."
        ],
      correctAnswer: "She kind of sort of maybe likes Chris A LOT more than she originally planned.",
    },
    {
      question: "Why does Xiaxin like Chris Smith?",
      incorrectAnswers: [
        "Because no one ignores her quite the way that he did",
        "Because no one travels faster than speed of light",
        "Actually she prefers CSS instead, regardless of how stunningly attractive Chris is",//"Because she likes CSS",
        "Because no one makes her less unhappy than him."
      ],
      correctAnswer:  "Because she wants to.",
    },
    {
      question: "What kind of things Xiaxin wants to do with Chris?",
      incorrectAnswers: [
        "She wants to watch talkshow with Chris every night",
        "She wants Chris and her to make fun of each other but never get tired of doing that",
        "She wants Chris and her to argue with each other and then give each other a bear hug",
      ],
      correctAnswer: "She wants to do all boring things with Chris",
    },
    {
      question: "What's Xiaxin's dream? Her dream is to ...",
      incorrectAnswers: [
          "have a dream in life", 
          "have a perfect weekend that lasts until next Friday", 
          "make all colleagues think she works super hard - even when she sometimes runs out of unproductive things to do at work but still pretends to be busy doing things she doesn't need to in order to avoid doing anything she's supposed to be doing."
        ],
      correctAnswer: "have a house with someone she likes where they each were doing their own things; if they came across something funny or intersting they stopped, shared it with each other, laughed about it, and went back to what they were doing...just like that growing old & disgusting with each other, and becoming each other's emergency contact person... It'd be awesome if that person were Chris Smith... sounds sweet ccoz it's just her dream life.",
    },
    {
      question: "When & Where did Chris and Xiaxin first met each other?",
      incorrectAnswers: [
        "Jan 12, 1990 & Putian, Fujian, China",
        "Oct 11, 2013 & Heysham 1 Power Station",
        "Jul 11, 2009 & Tesco Extra, Cardiff",
        "Sep 03, 2007 & Beijing, China "
      ],
      correctAnswer: "Jul 9, 2017 & Gloucester Leisure Center",
    },
    {
        question: "What's in Xiaxin's mind when she first met Chris Smith?",
        incorrectAnswers: [
          "Who am I? Where am I? Where am I from?",
          "What will I have for dinner tonight? Pork belly or salmon en croute? What have I got in my fridge?",
          "E=M*C^2 2H2+O2->2H2O e^x=1+x+x^2/2!+x^3/3!+... L{(e^-at)*cos(wt)*u(t)}=(s+a)/((s+a)^2+w^2) y^2=2px x^2+y^2-2*x=0 (x^2/a)+/-(y^2/b)=1 V.E=p/e0 V.B=0 VxE=-aB/at VxH=J+aD/at",
        ],
        correctAnswer: "Her heart fliped - in the first 2 secs her mind got blank. The whole world slowed down and everything around him just became blur. She could not take her eyes off Chris. felt like the time was frozen.",
      },
      {
        question: "When did Xiaxin stat to fancy Chris Smith?",
        incorrectAnswers: [
          "Just now",
          "Right after she first met him",
          "3.1415926 secs after she first met him",
        ],
        correctAnswer: "2 secs after she first met him",
      },
      {
        question: "What are the two bravest things Xiaxin has ever done or she never thought she'd do?",
        incorrectAnswers: [
          "Going study aboard, and getting a job offer after graduation",
          "Asking Charlie out to play badminton, and asking Chris for connecting on LinkedIn",
          "Initiating contact with Chris (via LinkedIn, then email, then text), and asking him out as an event manager",
        ],
        correctAnswer: "Baking birthday cakes (& cupcakes/muffines) for Chris' birthday, and planting a kiss on his cheek.",
      },
  ];
  
  export default data;